[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The family \u201cdelphinidae\u201d include which kind of cetacean?", "correct_answer": "Dolphins", "incorrect_answers": ["Rorqual whales", "Southern right whales", "Porpoises"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these Presidents had the most pets?", "correct_answer": "Theodore Roosevelt", "incorrect_answers": ["Franklin Delano Roosevelt", "Bill Clinton", "Woodrow Wilson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Adventures in Babysitting Sarah likes the superhero Thor.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This woman, who was the second wife and queen consort of Henry VIII, is said to have become a headless ghost after her death.", "correct_answer": "Anne Boleyn", "incorrect_answers": ["Mary Magdeline", "Mary Cox", "Anne Cox"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The song Everybody Wang Chung Tonight is playing in the background of the strip club where Ruth Lanier is working, when Chance comes in to question her.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The following citation is taken from this novel of F. Scott Fitzgerald. \nHe wanted not association with glittering things and glittering people \u2014 he wanted the glittering things themselves.", "correct_answer": "The Great Gatsby", "incorrect_answers": ["Tender Is the Night", "The Beautiful and Damned", "This Side of Paradise"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of this famous theorem?  If x, y, and z are non-zero positive integers, then x^n+y^n=z^n has no solution if n is an integer greater than two.", "correct_answer": "Fermats Theorem", "incorrect_answers": ["Gauss Theorem", "Eulers Theorem", "Riemanns Hypothesis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many feet are in a mile?", "correct_answer": "5280", "incorrect_answers": ["1770", "1000", "1665"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What vein is usually the first choice when selecting a site for venipuncture?", "correct_answer": "Median Cubital", "incorrect_answers": ["Accessory Cephalic", "Cephalic", "Basilic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Said to be the first of the Film Noir genre, The Maltese Falcon starred Humphrey Bogart as the one and only Sam Spade.  How many appearances did Bogart make as this character?", "correct_answer": "1", "incorrect_answers": ["3", "6", "4"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the nickname of the Gingerbread Man from the Shrek movies?", "correct_answer": "Gingy", "incorrect_answers": ["Baby", "Sugar", "Candy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these words means  gloomy, dark, sadly dim?", "correct_answer": "tenebrous", "incorrect_answers": ["insouciant", "qutianous", "prolix"]}]